<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Wanderlust & Wonder</title>
        <link>https://yourusername.github.io/your-repo</link>
        <description>Stories from travels, discoveries, and the beautiful chaos of life</description>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:41:06 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title>Researching El Norte de España</title>
            <link>https://yourusername.github.io/your-repo/researching-el-norte-de-espa-a.html</link>
            <description>There&#x27;s something about northern Spain that calls to me. Maybe it&#x27;s the rugged coastline, the ancient Celtic heritage, or the way the mountains meet the sea. I&#x27;ve been researching the region for months now, and each discovery makes me more eager to visit.

The Camino de Santiago has been on my bucket list forever, but I&#x27;m particularly drawn to the northern route - the Camino del Norte. It follows the coast from Irún to Santiago, passing through the Basque Country, Cantabria, Asturias, and Galici...</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid>https://yourusername.github.io/your-repo/researching-el-norte-de-espa-a.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Interesting Meeting in the Cement Museum</title>
            <link>https://yourusername.github.io/your-repo/interesting-meeting-in-the-cement-museum.html</link>
            <description>You know those places that sound completely random but turn out to be unexpectedly fascinating? The Cement Museum in Novorossiysk is exactly that.

Went there with friends on a whim - we were driving along the Black Sea coast and saw the sign. &quot;Cement Museum? Why not?&quot; we thought. Three hours later, we were still there, completely absorbed.

The museum is housed in what used to be an actual cement factory. The industrial architecture alone is worth the visit - these massive concrete structures t...</description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid>https://yourusername.github.io/your-repo/interesting-meeting-in-the-cement-museum.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Great Weekend in Almaty</title>
            <link>https://yourusername.github.io/your-repo/great-weekend-in-almaty.html</link>
            <description>Almaty never fails to surprise me. This weekend was particularly magical - the kind that makes you fall in love with a city all over again.

Started Saturday morning with a walk through Panfilov Park. The autumn leaves were at their peak, creating this golden carpet that crunched underfoot. Found a small café tucked away behind the opera house where they serve the most incredible samsa - flaky, buttery, and filled with perfectly spiced lamb.

The highlight was stumbling upon a local art market n...</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid>https://yourusername.github.io/your-repo/great-weekend-in-almaty.html</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>